https://www.kbc.be/retail/en/legal-information/privacy.html

file func document
General privacy statement for customers in the broad sense - KBC Bank NV
file func document
Annex to the KBC Data Protection Statement - automated decision-making
file func document
General privacy statement for customers in the broad sense - KBC Insurance NV
file func document
Annex to the Data Protection Statement - automated decision-making - KBC Insurance NV
file func document
General privacy statement - KBC Autolease NV
file func document
General privacy statement for clients in the broad sense and debtors - KBC Commercial Finance NV
file func document
Specific Privacy Statement on the Bancontact/Mister Cash Mobile App
file func document
General Privacy Statement of KBC Asset Management NV
file func document
General privacy statement for customers in the broad sense - CBC Banque SA (French)
file func document
General privacy statement for customers in the broad sense - KBC Securities NV
file func document
List of reinsurers of KBC Insurance NV
Was this page useful to you?
Report internet fraud
Attention, borrowing money also costs money.
Follow KBC on
Questions? KBC Live is there for you with fast answers.
Weekdays 8 a.m. to 10 p.m. – Saturdays 9 a.m. to 5 p.m.
KBC Live
Call a KBC Live expert
078 353 137
Get us to call you
Welcome!
NL
FR
DE
EN
We use cookies and similar technologies to make our website work better for you and ensure your online experience with us is more enjoyable and rewarding. We may also adapt our website to your needs and preferences. By continuing to use this website, you consent to our use of cookies.
Cookie statement
We really want you to always get the most from using our websites and applications (apps). That's why we like to tailor their content to better fit your needs and preferences. We use various techniques for this, including cookies, pixels, software development kits, local storage and similar technologies (collectively referred to below as 'cookies').
This cookie policy explains what cookies are, which ones we use, how you can change your cookie preferences and how we protect your privacy.
Whenever we refer to 'We/us/our' in this policy, we mean one of the entities listed in section 5 below.
1. What are cookies?
Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer, smartphone or tablet when you visit a website or use an app. They contain information like your preferred language for viewing a website, so you don't need to switch languages every time you visit it.
The cookies we sometimes use are:
Temporary (or session) cookies which are deleted when you close the browser or app
Permanent (or persistent) cookies that remain until they expire or you delete them (persistent cookies let us remember you when you come back to visit us, so you don't have to log in again every time)
First-party cookies used by one of our domains
Third-party cookies placed by other domains outside our organisation
See our detailed cookie list for more details.
2. Which cookies do we use and why?
We use three types of cookies on our websites.
Strictly necessary cookies
These cookies make mobile banking with us secure, ensure that our digital services work correctly and give you a more convenient experience with us. We need them for things like verifying your identity when you log in with us or remembering your preferred language. Your consent is not required for these cookies and you can't reject them as our digital services won't work without them.
Analysis/Performance cookies
These cookies collect information that helps us track how our digital services are used and make them even better. They tell us things like how many people use our digital services and for how long.
Other cookies
These include cookies that recognise you in order to record your preferences or behaviour for various purposes:
Functionality cookies make browsing more enjoyable, like ensuring that we don’t ask you to fill in a survey you’ve already completed.
Advertising and personalisation cookies collect information about your browsing habits with the aim of offering you advertising or content that may interest you.
Tracking cookies are used to track your behaviour on our websites and in our apps.
We use social media cookies to increase our relevance and to measure the efficiency of our advertising campaigns on social media platforms like Facebook, Instagram and LinkedIn
We may also use the data from other cookies for the purposes referred to above for our own carefully selected partners that offer banking and insurance products and services. An up-to-date list of these partners can be found at www.kbc.be/partners.
See our detailed cookie list for more details.
3. How do you choose the cookies that we place?
We'll give you as much control as we can. Please note that if you reject cookies, some parts of our digital services will be less adapted to your needs and preferences.
The various options are given below.
Websites
If you're visiting one of our websites for the first time, you can accept or reject cookies. If you wish to change this later, click 'Change cookie preference'.
Apps
If you're using one of our apps for the first time, you can accept or reject cookies. You can always change this later under Menu before you log into the app. Some of our apps also let you change this after you log in.
Browsers
You can disable cookies in your browser settings. Adjusting these settings varies according to the type of browser. Check the help feature of your browser or its user guide: Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Chrome and Safari.
Certain browsers allow you to choose not to be tracked by websites ('Do Not Track'). We only consider our own cookie mechanisms and do not support ‘Do Not Track’.
4. What about your privacy?
In any collaboration with third parties, we ensure that they can't identify you from the data we collect using cookies.
When we collect personal data through cookies, we always do so in accordance with our Data Protection Statement, which we recommend reading. In it, you can read that we use data from cookies, for instance, to create models and generate statistics that are subsequently applied generically to you individually or your family, or to other individuals.
We aim to fit our services as fully as possible to your needs and preferences. That's why we add personal data collected using cookies to information we already have on you. Conversely, we add a limited set of data (including the type of customer you are, your age group and your gender) from our systems to tailor our digital services to you. We only do so if you consent to the use cookies.
If you have accepted cookies for our digital services, but change your mind later:
We'll stop storing new data from the moment you reject cookies. If you change your cookie preference at a later time and give consent for their use again, we’ll add the new data to the previous data.
We’ll continue to use the data already stored if you have given your consent to the use of ‘personalised information’.
Find out more about personalised information in our KBC Data Protection Statement.
5. What companies does this cookie policy apply to and how can I get answers to questions and share feedback?
This cookie policy applies to the KBC group companies listed below.
The data controller for processing personal data depends on the digital service that you access or use.
When you access a third-party website through our digital services, their cookie policy applies. Our apps sometimes send you to third-party websites, like when you buy 'Additional services' using our Mobile app. In that case, the third-party's cookie policy also applies and we'll inform you accordingly. As the third party's own cookie policy applies, we recommend that you read their policy, as well.
Contact our support services to get more help with questions and share feedback. For complaints about exercising your rights, contact our Complaints Management team. You can e-mail us, write to us or send us a message online (including through our website, KBC Touch, Bolero Online or our Bolero app).
If our Complaints Management team can't answer your question, contact the relevant Data Protection Officer.
KBC Bank NV, Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels, Belgium - VAT BE 0462.920.226
First point of contact: Your KBC branch, your KBC Insurance agent or mypersonaldata@kbc.be
Complaints Management: Brusselsesteenweg 100, 3000 Leuven or complaints@kbc.be.
Data Protection Officer: KBC Bank NV, Group Data Protection Unit (Group Compliance), Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels, or dataprotection@kbc.be.
CBC Banque SA, Avenue Albert Ier 60, 5000 Namur, Belgium - VAT BE 0403.211.380
First point of contact: Your CBC branch, your CBC Insurance agent or gps@cbc.be
Complaints Management: Avenue Albert Ier, 60, 5000 Namur of gestiondesplaintes@cbc.be
Data Protection Officer: CBC Banque, Data Protection Officer (Group Compliance), avenue du Port 2, 1080 Bruxelles or dataprotection@kbc.be
KBC Insurance NV, Professor Roger Van Overstraetenplein 2, 3000 Leuven, Belgium - VAT BE 0403.552.563
First point of contact: Your KBC branch, your KBC Insurance agent or mypersonaldata@kbc.be
Complaints Management: Brusselsesteenweg 100, 3000 Leuven or complaints@kbc.be.
Data Protection Officer: KBC Bank NV, Group Data Protection Unit (Group Compliance), Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels, or dataprotection@kbc.be.
KBC Group NV, Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels, Belgium - VAT BE 0403.227.515
See points of contact for KBC Bank NV or CBC Banque SA.
KBC Asset Management NV, Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels, Belgium - VAT BE 0469.444.267
Complaints Management: opr.am@kbc.be
Data Protection Officer: KBC Asset Management NV, Complaints Officer (Company Risk Department), Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels or dataprotectionkbcam@kbc.be
KBC Fund Management Ltd., CPPI Team Sandwith Street, Dublin 2, D02 X489, Ireland - VAT 450585
Complaints Management: Complaints Officer, KBC Fund Management Ltd., Sandwith Street, Dublin 2, D02 X489, Ireland or kbcfm.complaints@kbcfm.com
KBC Securities NV, Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels, Belgium - VAT BE 0437.060.521
Data Protection Officer: KBC Securities, Data Protection Officer, Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels or compliancegroup@kbcsecurities.be
KBC Autolease NV, Professor Roger Van Overstraetenplein 5, 3000 Leuven, Belgium - VAT BE 0422.562.385
First point of contact: drivercare@kbcautolease.be
Complaints Management: complaints@kbc.be
Data protection Officer: KBC Autolease NV, Data Protection Officer, Prof. R. Van Overstraetenplein 5, 3000 Leuven or dataprotection@kbcautolease.be
KBC Lease Belgium NV, Brusselsesteenweg 100, 3000 Leuven, Belgium - VAT BE 0426.403.684
First point of contact: Your KBC branch, your KBC Insurance agent or mypersonaldata@kbc.be
Complaints Management: Brusselsesteenweg 100, 3000 Leuven or complaints@kbc.be
Data Protection Officer: KBC Bank NV, Group Data Protection Unit (Group Compliance), Havenlaan 2, 1080 Brussels, or dataprotection@kbc.be.
6. Conclusion
We may change this cookie policy at any time going forward; only the most recent version applies. We'll also inform you when there are important changes and will ask for your consent if necessary.
(Last updated on 29 February 2020)
Accept cookies
Reject cookies
More information on cookies
We use cookies and similar technologies to make our website work better for you and ensure your online experience with us is more enjoyable and rewarding. We may also adapt our website to your needs and preferences. By continuing to use this website, you consent to our use of cookies.
Learn more or reject cookies.
Keep browsing
